So I just feel the need to say it, smudge mascara and all.
Malcolm X was a wise, a brilliant, a passionate man.
He was not an infallible deity.
And the way in which folks will speak Malcolm's words as if to tell other folks
Malcolm said this and you will know is legit frightening to me because again, all of us
are human and Malcolm was speaking based on the time that he was in.
So has every great leader and visionary.
And then we, in the time that we're in, we look upon those words and we glean as much
as we can from them and also understand that we now know things that they didn't.
So in saying that, I honor the memory and the legacy of Malcolm X and also understand that
there are things he couldn't possibly have known, but that thanks to his teachings, we
are able to now know today.